Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
- UTU (United Transportation Union), Publication (Box 402, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: 70 Project seventies, Publication (Box 402, Folder 1)
    Author: Al H. Chesser
  - Item 10: An open letter to membership, 1965; Publication (Box 402, Folder 1)
    Author: Chicago Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union of Chicago and vicinity (Independent)
  - Item 11: Coal slurry handbook, Publication (Box 402, Folder 1)
- UTU (United Transportation Union), Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: And then came TWU!, 1950; Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: And then came TWU!: supplement, 1953; Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Official Directory of, 1965; Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
    Author: Transportation-Communication Employees Union
  - Item 4: Only TWU can win!, Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: You arbitrate this case! (preprinted from the May 1948 issue of Bus Transportation), Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Rank and File Transit News, 1950; Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.31, July 1950
  - Item 7: Report of Finance Committee to the Thirty-seventh regular and Fourth quadrennial session of the Grand Division, 1968; Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: TWU and civil rights: "regardless of race, creed, color or nationality"., 1965; Publication (Box 402, Folder 2)
- TWU (Transport Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: This is your union, Publication (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: TWU and the fight for civil rights, 1934-1963, Publication (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Pan American navigators ask company: "don't be artibrary, Arbitrate!", Publication (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: America's greatest crisis, 1961; Publication (Box 402, Folder 3)
    Author: Martin Luther King, Jr.
    Notes: Address by Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King to the 11th Constitutional Convention, TWU (Transport Workers Union of America), AFL-CIO.
  - Item 5: ATD-TWU and jet safety, Publication (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The big grab: the facts behind the proposed American/Eastern Airline merger, Publication (Box 402, Folder 3)
- TWU (Transport Workers Union of America), Publication (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The big grab: the facts behind the proposed American/Eastern Airline merger, Publication (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: flyer - End the American tragedy!, Publication (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: article from TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 402, Folder 4)
    Notes: Article. June, 1963.
  - Item 4: TWU Legislative Report, 1963; Publication (Box 402, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.5- 8
- ITU (International Typographical Union)., Publication (Box 403, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Arbitrations - New York Typographical Union Number 6 and Publishers' Assoc. of NYC, 1960-1969 (Box 403, Folder 1)
    Notes: From New York World-Telegram and Sun
- ITU (International Typographical Union)., Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of arbitration proceedings between the Employing Printers' Association, Closed Shop Division (Printers' League) New York City and Typographical Union No. 6, 1921; Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: partial agreement - Arbitration agreement, between the American Newspaper Publishers' Association and the International Typographical Union, 1907; Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Arbitration proceedings and the findings and award of William E. Kelly, arbitrator, in re Typographical Union No. 6 versus the Publishers' Association, 1920; Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
    Author: William E. Kelly
  - Item 4: Arbitration proceedings and the findings and award of Frank Morrison, arbitrator, in re Typographical Union No. 6 versus the Publishers' Association, 1919; Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
    Author: Frank Morrison
  - Item 5: The Chicago Press feeders' wage arbitration case, Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Arbitration proceedings: New York Typographical Union No. 6 and American Newspaper Publishers' Ass'n., 1907; Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Award and opinions of arbitrators: in the matter of the arbitration between Grandview Dairy, Inc. and Milk Wagon Drivers' Union, Local 584 in its own behalf and in behalf of each individual member of the union at the time of the alleged violation of the c, 1939; Publication (Box 403, Folder 2)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 403, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your group insurance plan, 1975; Publication (Box 403, Folder 3)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union). No. 6 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 2: Retirement trust plan: resolution of the Executive Council, 1974; Publication (Box 403, Folder 3)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union)
  - Item 3: Negotiated pension plan: agreement and declaration of trust, 1974; Publication (Box 403, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Negotiated pension plan (Canada): agreement and declaration of trust, 1974; Publication (Box 403, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: America needs labor unions, 1960; Publication (Box 403, Folder 3)
    Author: Elmer Brown
  - Item 6: ITU: negotiated pension plan, 1973; Publication (Box 403, Folder 3)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Empire Typographical and Mailer Conference, 1978; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1946; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 1946.
  - Item 3: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1952; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 1952.
  - Item 4: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1953; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 1953.
  - Item 5: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1955; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
    Notes: March 1955.
  - Item 6: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1957; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
    Notes: June 1957.
  - Item 7: Printing Industry - Chicago --- The decision of Hon. H. Frank Pennington, arbitrator in the case of the closed shop division of the Franklin Assoc, Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Shop Rules and Wage Scales - Contract, 1961-1963 (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Arbitration and proceedings: New York Typographical Union No. 6 and American Newspaper Publishers' Ass'n., 1907; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Before an arbitration board: Franklin Association of Chicago, Plaintiff, vs. Chicago Typographical Union, No. 16, Defendant: Closing arguments for the defendant, 1922; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Arbitration and proceedings and the findings and award of before George W. Kirchwey, Arbitrator in re Typographical Union No. 6 versus Employing Printers' Association, Closed Shop Division (Printers' League) Branch, 1920; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Arbitration and proceedings and the findings and award of before Judge Alfred J. Talley, Arbitrator between Closed Shop (Printers' League) Branch, New York Employing Printers' Association, Inc. and Typographical Union No. 6, 1922; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Empire Typographical Conference: Official Call, Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Centenary Banquet of the New York Typographical Society, 1909; Publication (Box 403, Folder 4)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: News Release - Biographical sketch of Elmer Brown, Publication (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: America needs labor unions, 1960; Publication (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: ITU and the Communications Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 404, Folder 1)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1962; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1963; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1964; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1965; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1966; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1967; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1968; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Official Directory of the International Typographical Union, 1974; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: correspondence - To: Mr. C. Raymond Hulsart, The New York Times, 1962; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
    Author: Townley, Updike, Carter & Rodgers
  - Item 10: Los Angeles Mailers Union No. 9, International Typograpraphical Union (AFL-CIO), Petitioner, v. National Labor Relations Board, Respondent: on petition to review and set aside and on cross- petition to enforce an order of the National Labor Relations Board, 1960; Publication (Box 404, Folder 2)
    Author: International Typograpraphical Union
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: One Hundred Eighth Semi-Annual convention, 1972; Publication (Box 404, Folder 3)
    Author: Empire Typographical and Mailer Conference
  - Item 2: 86th Semi-Annual Conference, 1961; Publication (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Apprentice regulations: a guide for local officers and committees, 1962; Publication (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Speaker's manual: for ITU officers, representatives, public relations committees, members, and all who would tell the ITU story "2", 1961; Publication (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Speaker's manual: for ITU officers, representatives, public relations committees, members, and all who would tell the ITU story "1", 1961; Publication (Box 404, Folder 3)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Face the facts today and avoid a crisis tomorrow; Report from Executive Council on National Industrial Pension Plan, Publication (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Modern printing, 1968; Publication (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: 100 years plus of democratic trade unionism, 1960; Publication (Box 404, Folder 4)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union). Executive Council
  - Item 4: 110 years plus of democratic trade unionism: the story of the International Typographical Union, 1962; Publication (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: 114 years plus of democratic trade unionism: the story of the International Typographical Union, 1966; Publication (Box 404, Folder 4)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 112 years plus of democratic trade unionism: the story of the International Typographical Union, 1965; Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Correspondence - to Mr. James H. Sampson, Pres. Executive Council of the ITU appreciates your early response, 1967; Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Empire Typographical and Mailer Conference - Ond Hundred Ninth semi-annual convention, 1973; Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: One little label and how it grew, Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: ITU Fraternal benefit, Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Facts about the International Typographical Union for all who would like to know, 1959; Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Facts about the International Typographical Union for all who would like to know, 1960; Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Facts about the International Typographical Union for all who would like to know, 1961; Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Facts about the International Typographical Union for all who would like to know, 1962; Publication (Box 404, Folder 5)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 404, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Dues circular, 1947; Publication (Box 404, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The I-T-U's Modern Defense Activities., 1951; Publication (Box 404, Folder 6)
- Joint Council of Women's Auxiliaries of St. Louis, Mo., Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence - Dear Mrs. Mooney, While the attached circular tells of what some outstanding people, 1965; Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
    Author: Joint Council of Women's Auxiliaries of St. Louis, Mo.
    Notes: Photocopy
  - Item 2: The Big Six Picket, 1962; Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.1-8
  - Item 3: Storm Center of New York paper strike: a tough union tactician named Powers, 1962; Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Mary E. Ryder is named St. Louis Woman of Year, 1954; Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Mrs. Mary E. Ryder to get Women's C. of C. Award; Woman of the year, 1954; Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Mrs. Mary E Ryder, President of Local Joint Council in charge of convention - Feb. 26th and 27th, 1932; Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: In our town with Bob Goddard, Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Into their own nets by Mary E. Ryder, Publication (Box 405, Folder 1)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Scale of prices, 1948-1949 (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Scale of prices, 1958-1960 (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report of the Land Committee of, 1898; Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Typographical Review, 1916; Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Bibliothek der Typograph No. 7, 1907; Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Tarif der Typograph No. 7, 1916-1917 (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The New York situation, 1919; Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
    Notes: Issued by direction of New York Typographical Union No. 6
  - Item 8: The enemy within!, 1925; Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Heads I winTails you lose; with either Rouse of Hewson as President, the employers win, Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: In memoriam Amos D. Cummings., 1902; Publication (Box 405, Folder 2)
    Notes: Program from memorial service
  - Item 11: Scale of prices, 1947-1948 (Box 405, Folder 2)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Program from the Sixty-Fifth convention in Albany, NY, August 9th-14th, 1920, Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union) Local 4 (Albany, N.Y.)
  - Item 2: It should, it can it shall be done!, 1961; Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Big 6, Printers League go to school for their mutual benefit, 1967; Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Progressive Program - Candidates - Record, Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
    Author: New York Progressive Club
  - Item 5: The question at hand involves the comprehensive medical features of the Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
    Author: Typo- Publishers' Welfare Fund
  - Item 6: The New York Progressive, 1961; Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
    Notes: May, 1961.
  - Item 7: Shop rules and scales for New York Typographical Union No. 6, I.T.U., Mailers' Union No. 6, I.T.U., Printing Pressmen's Union No. 51, I.P.P. & A.U., New York Job Pressmen & Job Press Feeders' Union No. 1, I.P.P. & A. U., Paper Cutters' Union No. 119, I.B., 1921; Publication (Box 405, Folder 3)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 405, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Big Six Picket, 1962-1963 (Box 405, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.9-52
  - Item 2: To the Members of NY - Your newspaper Scale Committee presents this proposal and recommends its approval., 1960; Publication (Box 405, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Book and Job Branch, Publication (Box 405, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Now hear this!, Publication (Box 405, Folder 4)
- Phliadelphia Typographical Union No. 2, Publication (Box 405, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Typographical Record, 1960; Publication (Box 405, Folder 5)
    Author: International Progressive Party
    Notes: January 1960.
  - Item 2: 100th Anniv. (souvenir program), 1950; Publication (Box 405, Folder 5)
    Author: Albany Typographical Union No. 4
    Notes: Program
  - Item 3: Diamond Jubilee, 1925; Publication (Box 405, Folder 5)
    Author: Phliadelphia Typographical Union No. 2
  - Item 4: A study of actual earnings in Philadelphia Typographical Union, Number 2, 1928; Publication (Box 405, Folder 5)
    Author: Jurgen Kuczynski
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: "Instructions and advice pursuant to decree in contempt", 1948; Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: The Injunction against I.T.U., Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Facts concerning the International Typographical Union beneficial features and other interesting data (serial) [12th, 13th, 15th, 16th], Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
    Author: J. W. Hays
  - Item 4: Facts concerning the international Typographical Union, 1938; Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Facts concerning the international Typographical Union, 1945; Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Facts International Typographical Union Beneficial Features & Interesting data (9th ), 1913; Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Epochal history of the International typographical union, 1925; Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
    Author: James M. Lynch
  - Item 8: Excerpts from the testimony of Woodruff Randolph and oral argument by attorney Van Arkel, 1948; Publication (Box 405, Folder 6)
    Author: Woodruff Randolph; Gerhard P. Van Arkel
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Epochal history of the International typographical union, 1925; Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Facts about the International Typographical Union for all who would like to know (1952), Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: 110 years plus of democratic trade unionism: the story of the International Typographical Union, 1962; Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: 114 years plus of democratic trade unionism: the story of the International Typographical Union, 1966; Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: ITU Review (souvenir edition), 1962; Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: article- General laws of the International Typographical Union -, 1959; Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Zu Schutz und Trutz! 25 jahrige Geschichte der deutsch-amerikanischen Typographia; 1. Juli 1873-bis 30. Juni 1898. Ein Beitrag zur amerikanischen, Publication (Box 405, Folder 7)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Miami Union Printer, 1952; Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
    Notes: August 16, 1952.
  - Item 2: Miami Union Printer, 1949-1952 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.36; v.3:no.19-20; v.4:no.1, 11- 12
  - Item 3: Scale of prices, 1949-1950 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Scale of prices, 1952-1953 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Contract and scale for Daily Newspapers, Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Contract between Quality Press and the International Typographical Union of the City of Binghamton, 1923; Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Contract and scale for book and job offices, Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Scale of prices between the Publishers of Binghamton, NY and Binghaton Typographical Union, Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Contract between Quality Press and the International Typographical Union of the City of Binghamton, 1924; Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Contract between Knight & Palmer and the International Typographical Union of the City of Binghamton, 1917- 1921 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Contract and scale for Daily Newspapers, 1917; Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Scale of prices between Commercial Printers of Binghamton, NY and Binghamton Typographical Union, No. 232, Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Scale of prices between the Endicott Daily Bulletin and Binghamton Typographical Union, No. 232, Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Scale of prices between Endicott Daily Bulletin and Binghamton typographical Union No. 232, 1948-1950 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Scale of prices between Commercial Printers and Binghamton Typographical Union, No. 232, 1948-1949 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Newspaper contract and scale of prices between the Endicott Daily Bulletin and Binghamton Typographical Union No. 232, 1953- 1954 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: One hundred years 1852-1952, Publication (Box 406, Folder 1)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union) Local 9 (Buffalo, N.Y.)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 406, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Reporter - Forty-third year -no. 1-11; Forty-second year - no.6-12, 1948-1949 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union). Local 16 (Chicago, Ill.)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 406, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Official Souvenir book: 70th Anniversary, 1920; Publication (Box 406, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Official Souvenir book: 90th Anniversary., 1940; Publication (Box 406, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Official Souvenir book: 100th Annivsary., 1950; Publication (Box 406, Folder 3)
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Government by injunction!, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Why not in Chicago?, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Facts on the Printers' Strike against the Chicago Newspapers, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Don't buy injunction newspaers!, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The true story of teh defender strike, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Let's take a look at the Defender case, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Which side are you on?, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: The Picket's voice, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: A statement by R.G. Soderstrom..., Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Trade unionists..., Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Correspondence - An Open Letter to All Holy Name Societies - This is written in behalf of striking newspaper printers, many of whom are members of Holy Name societies of their respective parishes, 1948; Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Meet the Union Printers, 1948-1949 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    Notes: Radio show transcript
  - Item 13: Report of Hammond Times Newspaper Scale Committee, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Injunction threat brings new aid to striking printers, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: 1600 newspaper printers are on strike in Chicago, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Trade unionists: the Michigan Chronicle unfair to union labor, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Louisville Citizens: Louisville defender and Frank Stanley, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Facts about the Printers' Strike, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: A message from the Union Printers on strike against the newspapers, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Guinea pigs - Chicago Publishers..., Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: The Picket, 1947-1949 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.1-13, 16-41
  - Item 22: Lakeside Bulletin, 1947; Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (1947)
  - Item 23: Other unions rally to aid of Chicago's typo strikers, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: Chicago dailies hard hit by printers' walkout, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Pensioned printers aid in Chicago strike, Publication (Box 406, Folder 4)